[♪♪♪]
I'm Peppa Pig. Oink.
This my little brother, George.
Oink, oink.
This is Mummy Pig.
Oink.
And this
is Daddy Pig.
Oink!
[ALL LAUGHING]
Peppa Pig. Oink.
[♪♪♪]
[PEPPA READS ONSCREEN TEXT]
[BOTH LAUGHING]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and George are helping
Grandpa Pig in his Garden.
Wow.
Oh.
NARRATOR:
What a beautiful butterfly.
[♪♪♪]
Oink. Grandpa, why do
butterflies like flowers?
Oink. They get their food
from flowers.
How?
They have very long tongues.
Longer than mine? Pfft.
Ha, ho. Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Oink.
Oh, yes, the butterfly's tongue
is even longer than yours.
She uses it to drink
from the flower.
[SLURPS AND BURPS]
[PEPPA & GEORGE LAUGH]
Wow.
GRANDPA:
Ho, ho. Peppa, the butterfly
thinks you're a flower.
[LAUGHS]
I'm not a flower.
I'm Peppa Pig. Oink.
[♪♪♪]
Heh-heh-heh.
She is so pretty.
Oink. I want to be
a butterfly. Heh-heh-heh-heh.
NARRATOR:
Peppa is playing
at being a butterfly.
I'm a little butterfly.
Oink. Oink.
NARRATOR:
George wants to play, too.
[LAUGHING AND OINKING]
George,
I'm the butterfly.
You have to be
something else.
[♪♪♪]
Oink. I know. You can be
a wriggly worm.
[LAUGHING]
Look, look.
I'm a butterfly. Oink.
[CRYING]
NARRATOR:
Oh, dear.
George does not want
to be a worm.
He wants to be a butterfly.
George. When I was
a little piggy,
I used to like playing
at being a worm.
Oink. It's very easy
to be a worm.
I'll show you how.
[♪♪♪]
First you have
to lie down on the ground.
Then, you wriggle around.
[LAUGHS]
I'm a wriggly worm! Oink.
[GEORGE & GRANDPA LAUGHING]
Oink, oink.
NARRATOR:
George and Grandpa Pig
are having such fun
being wriggly worms.
[LAUGHS]
I'm a little butterfly.
Oink.
[GRANDPA PIG & GEORGE LAUGHING]
Look, look.
I'm a butterfly.
Yes Peppa, you're
a beautiful butterfly.
[GEORGE & GRANDPA LAUGH]
Oink.
Grandpa. George.
What are
you doing?
We are wriggly worms.
[GEORGE & GRANDPA LAUGH]
Oink. I want to be
a wriggly worm, too.
I'm a wriggly worm.
Oink, oink.
[ALL LAUGHING]
I'm a wriggly worm.
Ha, ha. I'm a wriggly worm.
How do you do?
I love you.
I'm a wriggly worm.
Oink.
[ALL LAUGHING]
That was fun. Oink.
What animal
do you want to be now?
Hmm.
I don't know.
Croak.
PEPPA:
Look, Grandpa.
There's a little frog.
Croak.
Why don't you play
at being frogs?
Hmm, frogs
are not as pretty
as butterflies
or as wriggly as worms.
But frogs do play
a game you like.
Hmm. Do frogs
play doll's houses?
Ho-ho-ho. Silly Peppa.
What's your favorite game?
Jumping in muddy puddles!
Oink. Oink.
GRANDPA:
Yes. Frogs love
jumping in muddy puddles.
Croak.
[♪♪♪]
Oink. Yes, George.
Let's play frogs.
Croak.
I'm a little froggy.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
Croak. Croak.
[ALL LAUGHING]
NARRATOR:
The froggies have found a nice
big muddy puddle to play in.
Peppa and George love jumping
up and down in muddy puddles.
Everyone loves jumping up
and down in muddy puddles.
Oink. Butterflies and worms
are very nice. Oink.
But I like frogs the best.
Croak.
[ALL PIGS LAUGHING AND OINKING]
[FROG CROAKING]
[♪♪♪]
[PEPPA READS ONSCREEN TEXT]
[BOTH LAUGHING]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and George are playing
in Mummy and Daddy's bedroom.
Oink. What's this?
NARRATOR:
Peppa has found
a box of old clothes.
Wow. Oink.
This is Daddy's hat.
And this is Mummy's dress.
George. Let's dress up and
pretend to be Mummy and Daddy.
Oink, oink.
PEPPA:
Here is Daddy's hat.
[LAUGHS]
And here
is Daddy's coat.
[LAUGHS]
Oink. Hello,
Daddy Pig.
Oink.
[BOTH LAUGH]
Now it's my turn.
Oink. This is
Mummy's dress.
[BOTH LAUGH]
This is Mummy's hat.
Oink.
[PEPPA & GEORGE LAUGHING]
Daddy Pig.
Where are your shoes?
Oink.
[♪♪♪]
[PEPPA & GEORGE LAUGHING]
Oink. I need
some shoes, too.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
Now I need to look beautiful.
Just like Mummy.
[♪♪♪]
NARRATOR:
Peppa has found
Mummy's make-up box.
Aha.
[LAUGHS]
First some powder.
Oink. Lovely.
Now for some lipstick.
What a pretty Mummy Pig.
Oink.
[LAUGHS]
Come along, Daddy Pig.
It's time to go to work.
[PEPPA & GEORGE
OINKING AND LAUGHING]
NARRATOR:
Mummy is working
on her computer.
[LAUGHING]
Hello, Peppa.
Hello, George.
I beg your pardon?
Peppa, I was
just saying hello.
Oink. I'm not
Peppa Pig.
I'm Mummy Pig.
Oh, yes!
Of course.
Hello, Mummy Pig.
Hello. Oink.
And this
is Daddy Pig.
George.
Oink!
And hello to you too,
Daddy Pig.
[PEPPA & GEORGE GIGGLING]
Excuse me. I've got
a lot of work to do.
Hello. Yes, do this, do that.
No, thank you, goodbye.
Oink! Heh-heh-heh.
NARRATOR:
Peppa is enjoying
pretending to be Mummy Pig.
But George is getting
a bit bored.
Oink.
Sorry, Daddy Pig.
I'm nearly finished.
[COMPUTER BEEPING]
There. All done!
Come on, Daddy Pig.
It's time you did some work.
Goodbye, Mummy Pig
and Daddy Pig.
Goodbye.
Oink.
[PEPPA & GEORGE LAUGHING]
[♪♪♪]
NARRATOR:
Daddy Pig is digging
in the garden.
[PEPPA & GEORGE LAUGHING]
Oink.
Hello, Peppa.
Hello, George.
Oink.
I'm not Peppa.
I'm Mummy Pig
and this is Daddy Pig.
Oink!
Daddy Pig is here
to do some work.
That's very kind
of you Daddy Pig. Oink.
Now be careful,
it's a very deep hole.
[♪♪♪]
[PEPPA & DADDY PIG LAUGH]
Oink. I do hope
you are not digging
in your best clothes,
Daddy Pig.
[LOUDLY ECHOES]
Oink!
[DADDY PIG & PEPPA LAUGH]
I want to make big snorts, too.
[LAUGHS]
[LOUDLY ECHOES]
Oinks!
[PEPPA & GEORGE LAUGHING
AND OINKING LOUDLY]
[♪♪♪]
Ice cream, everyone.
Ice cream!
Peppa. George.
You must take off those muddy
clothes before you eat.
Oink. I'm Mummy Pig
and this is Daddy Pig.
MUMMY:
Are you sure?
Yes.
So, where are
Peppa and George?
We don't know.
Oh, well that's a shame,
because I've got
their favorite ice cream here.
But if we can't
find them then...
Oink.
Here we are!
Peppa!
George!
There you are!
Yes, Mummy. We were just
pretending to be you and Daddy.
Oh, ho-ho-ho.
You really had us fooled.
[ALL LAUGHING AND OINKING]
[♪♪♪]
[PEPPA READS ONSCREEN TEXT]
[BOTH LAUGHING]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and George have been
playing in the garden.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
Oink.
Peppa, where are
your shoes?
Oh. I've lost them.
Well, I'm sure
we can find them. Oink.
Maybe we should
try the garden?
Oink. Yes!
[♪♪♪]
NARRATOR:
Everyone is looking
for Peppa's shoes.
Mummy Pig is looking
in the flowerbed.
Peppa's shoes are not there.
Oh.
NARRATOR:
Daddy Pig is looking
in the wheelbarrow.
Peppa's shoes are not there.
Oh.
NARRATOR:
Peppa and George
look in the flowerpots.
Peppa's shoes
are not there either.
Oh.
Oink. We've looked everywhere,
but we can't find Peppa's shoes.
NARRATOR:
Peppa's shoes are lost.
Now I haven't got
any shoes to wear. Oink.
Poor, Peppa. Your shoes were
getting a bit old. Oink.
We'll buy
you a new pair!
Oink. Can my new shoes
be red, Mummy?
Of course they can.
George! I'm going to have
new red shoes!
Oink. Oink.
[♪♪♪]
NARRATOR:
Mummy Pig and Peppa
are at Miss Rabbit's shoe shop.
Hello,
Miss Rabbit.
Mummy Pig.
Oink. We would like to buy some
new shoes for Peppa, please.
Oink. Red shoes.
Oh, I'm sure we can find you
some lovely new shoes, Peppa.
Red ones. Oink. Please.
Of course. Red ones.
Wow!
[♪♪♪]
Oink. Oink. New red shoes!
[LAUGHS]
NARRATOR:
George and Daddy Pig
are playing draughts.
Oink, oink.
Oh, well done, George.
Daddy! Daddy!
Ha-ha-ha. Oink.
Look at
my new shoes!
They're red!
I say! They are red.
Oink. Mummy, do you
like my new shoes?
Yes, Peppa they make
you look very smart.
Oink. George.
Do you like my new shoes?
Oink. Oink.
NARRATOR:
Everyone likes
Peppa's new shoes.
I like my new shoes
so much
I don't want
to ever take them off.
[ALL LAUGH]
[♪♪♪]
NARRATOR:
It is bath time.
Peppa wants to keep her new
shoes on, even for her bath.
[LAUGHS]
NARRATOR:
Peppa is in her pajamas.
She still has her new shoes on.
[LAUGHS]
NARRATOR:
Peppa even wants to wear
her new shoes in bed!
Peppa, are you sure you don't
want to take your shoes off?
I don't want to ever take
my new shoes off, Mummy.
Ha. Very well.
Goodnight, Peppa and George.
[LAUGHS AND OINKS]
Ha-ha-ha. Goodnight,
Mummy. Oink.
Goodnight, Daddy.
Oink. Goodnight,
my little piggies.
[RAIN POURING]
NARRATOR:
It has been raining all night,
and now the garden is very wet.
Mummy Pig is wearing her boots.
Daddy Pig is
wearing his boots.
George is wearing his boots.
Peppa is still wearing
her new red shoes.
[LAUGHS AND OINKS]
NARRATOR:
George is going to play
in the wet grass.
[LAUGHING]
NARRATOR:
Oh, dear.
Peppa loves playing
in the wet grass,
but she doesn't want get
her new shoes wet.
I can't play
in the wet grass, George.
Oh. Oink. Oink.
[♪♪♪]
NARRATOR:
George loves jumping
in muddy puddles.
Oink. Oink.
NARRATOR:
Peppa loves jumping in puddles,
but she doesn't want
to get her new shoes muddy.
Oh.
NARRATOR:
Mummy and Daddy love jumping up
and down in in muddy puddles.
Everyone likes jumping
in muddy puddles.
Oink.
[♪♪♪]
NARRATOR:
Where is Peppa going?
Oink, oink.
[LAUGHS]
NARRATOR:
Peppa is putting on her boots.
[LAUGHING]
Oink, oink.
[CONTINUES LAUGHING]
Oink.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Whee!
If you jump in muddy puddles,
you must wear your boots.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[♪♪♪]
[PEPPA READS ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
Today is day
of the school fete.
Peppa loves coming to the fete.
[LAUGHING]
NARRATOR:
Here are Peppa's friends,
Candy Cat, Suzy Sheep,
Danny Dog, Rebecca Rabbit
and Pedro Pony.
Hello, everyone. Oink.
ALL [GRUNTING]:
Hello, Peppa.
I love the school fete.
Me, too. Oink.
What do you like best?
Bleat. The face
painting.
Whinny.
I like the balloons.
Woof, woof. I like
the bouncy castle the best.
I like everything. Oink.
Ho, ho. A very good
choice, Peppa.
Woof. See you
later, Peppa.
Oink. See you later.
George, what do you like best?
Dine-saw. Grrr.
Oh dear, there aren't any
dinosaurs at the fete, George.
Maybe we can get
you a dinosaur balloon.
Are you sure they have dinosaur
balloons, Daddy Pig?
I'm certain of it.
Oink.
Can George and I get
our faces painted first?
Of course.
[PEPPA & GEORGE LAUGH]
NARRATOR:
Miss Rabbit has painted
Peppa's friends as tigers.
There you are, Suzy.
Now you look
like a tiger.
Thank you, Miss Rabbit. Bleat.
[PEPPA & GEORGE LAUGH]
Wow! I like
your face, Suzy.
Are you a pussycat?
No! I'm a tiger!
Bleat.
Peppa, would you like
your face painted?
Yes, please.
Can I be...an elephant?
Oh dear, I don't know
how to do elephants.
I can do tigers.
[ALL LAUGH]
Yes, a tiger please.
There you are Peppa,
now you're a tiger.
Ha-ha-ha. I'm a tiger. Oink.
George, what would
you like to be?
Dine-saw. Grrr.
A dinosaur?
Uh, how about
a tiger instead?
I'm good at tigers.
Oink. Oink.
Ha-ha-ha.
I'm a tiger. Oink.
So am I.
Woof. Woof.
Meow. Tigers don't
say, "Woof, woof."
How do you know?
Because tigers are big cats.
Meow. And I'm a cat.
Candy, please can you teach us
how to be tigers?
Okay.
Tigers creep very, very slowly
and then, they jump.
Grrr.
[ALL SCREAM]
[ALL LAUGH]
ALL:
Grrr.
Tigers like to lick
themselves clean.
[SLURPS]
But, best of all, when tigers
are happy, they purr.
[PURRS]
[ALL PURR]
Hello, children.
Oh. My goodness.
You're all tigers.
And I'm teaching them
to be proper tigers.
Grrr.
[LAUGHS]
What do you little tigers
want to do next?
Oink. Dine-saw.
That's right. We have to find
George a dinosaur balloon.
[LAUGHS]
Let's get
you all balloons.
ALL:
Hooray!
[ALL LAUGHING]
Hello, Madame Gazelle.
We'd like
some balloons, please.
Certainly.
I've got lots
of different ones.
Can I have an elephant
balloon, please?
Here you are, Peppa.
Can I have a kangaroo?
A lion, please.
A monkey, please.
A parrot, please.
Ho, ho. Yes, I've
got all those.
[ALL LAUGH]
Most important
of all,
we need a dinosaur
balloon for George.
Oh dear, I do not seem to have
any dinosaur balloons.
Oh.
[CRYING]
Don't worry, George. I've got
an idea.
Could we have two of the long
balloons, please?
Watch this,
everybody.
[♪♪♪]
NARRATOR:
What is Daddy Pig
doing with the balloons?
There. Can anyone
guess what it is?
Is it a kangaroo?
Ho, ho. No, it's a--
Dine-saw.
DADDY:
That's right. A dinosaur.
NARRATOR:
Daddy Pig has made
a balloon dinosaur.
Grrr. Dine-saw.
Oink.
Now the bouncy castle!
[KIDS LAUGHING]
NARRATOR:
Peppa loves bouncing
on the bouncy castle.
Everyone loves bouncing
This is the best school
fete, ever.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[♪♪♪]
♪ Peppa Pig
Oink ♪
[PEPPA LAUGHS AND OINKS]
♪ Peppa Pig
Oink ♪
[MORE LAUGHING AND OINKING]
♪ Peppa Pig
Oink ♪